[
    {
        "question": "He no longer ............ as he used to do.",
        "choices": [
            "smoke",
            "smokes",
            "smoked",
            "doesn't smoke"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "smoke"
    },
    {
        "question": "He used to smoke but now he ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "isn't anymore",
            "doesn't no longer",
            "doesn't any longer",
            "any longer doesn't"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "doesn't any longer"
    },
    {
        "question": "He was used to smoking, but now he ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "is no longer",
            "no longer is",
            "does no longer",
            "no longer does"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "no longer is"
    },
    {
        "question": "A: Does he smoke? B: No, but he ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "is used to",
            "is used to doing",
            "used to do",
            "used to be"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "is used to"
    },
    {
        "question": "A: Is he used to smoking? B: No, but he ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "is used to",
            "is used to doing",
            "used to do",
            "used to be"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "is used to doing"
    },
    {
        "question": "A: ............ ? B: Yes, but he never smokes now.",
        "choices": [
            "Is he used to smoking",
            "Does he get used to smoking",
            "Did he use to smoke",
            "Was he used to smoke"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Is he used to smoking"
    },
    {
        "question": "I wish you ............ your time last year.",
        "choices": [
            "wasted",
            "didn't waste",
            "had wasted",
            "hadn't wasted"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "didn't waste"
    },
    {
        "question": "............. to bed before 1 a.m.",
        "choices": [
            "Rarely do I go",
            "I go rarely",
            "Rarely I go",
            "Rarely am I go"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Rarely do I go"
    },
    {
        "question": "He never ............ used to eating in class.",
        "choices": [
            "is",
            "was",
            "got",
            "get"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "get"
    },
    {
        "question": "It's a habit of ............ to drink a big glass of water when I get up every morning.",
        "choices": [
            "I",
            "me",
            "my",
            "mine"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "I"
    }
]